http://www.piccadilly.com/privacy-policy/

Locations
Find the nearest Piccadilly:
Gift Cards
Your location is not set.
Click here to set your location.
Privacy Policy
THE INTERNET, PRIVACY, AND PICCADILLY.COM
The Internet contains a wealth of information; unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don't want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos, or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. When you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge. At Piccadilly.com we strive to help our guests protect their privacy while using our services.
PICCADILLY.COM'S PRIVACY POLICY
Piccadilly.com's policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so.
Piccadilly.com will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. However, Piccadilly.com may disclose user information under special circumstances that include, but not limited to:
Occasions when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Piccadilly.com's rights or property, other Piccadilly.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
Situations when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.. Piccadilly.com shares aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we will say Piccadilly.com's audience is x percent female and y percent male. This data is used to customize Piccadilly.com's content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.
Piccadilly.com shares aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we will say Piccadilly.com's audience is x percent female and y percent male. This data is used to customize Piccadilly.com's content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.
There are cases where Piccadilly.com may ask you for personal information such as your name, e-mail address, and birth date. For example, we request personal information for online shopping or transactions, or for services that require registration or subscription. Piccadilly.com needs to collect this information for tracking/verifying compliance with Piccadilly.com policies as well as federal, state, and local laws, and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes.
In case you change your mind or some personal information changes (such as your ZIP code), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the personal data you give us. You can do this by contacting our Guest Services at GuestServices@Piccadilly.com.
OPTING OUT
Information provided at the time of Registration or submission from a Guest who is 13 years of age or over may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by Piccadilly.com and our affiliates or companies that have been prescreened by Piccadilly.com. To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt out of the following services: receiving communications from Piccadilly.com about new features or services, and receiving communications about offers from third-party companies that offer a product or service that we think would be of value to you. If a Guest objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use -- either by e-mail request to GuestServices@Piccadilly.com. Information provided when purchasing products from any of our online stores may be used for marketing and promotional purposes and is subject to the opt-out processes described on, or linked to, each order form.
POLICIES FOR KIDS (INDIVIDUALS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE)
Piccadilly.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered on the sites. No information should be submitted to or posted at Piccadilly.com by Guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.
Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Piccadilly.com does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from our Guests less than 13 years of age. All registrants receive an e-mail confirming their Registration. In addition, when a Guest under 13 registers, he/she is required to provide the e-mail address of his/her parent or guardian and that parent or guardian receives an e-mail alerting them to that Registration. Since all of Piccadilly.com's free interactive activities are monitored by community policy experts, registered Guests under 13 years of age may participate in such activities upon Registration, unless their parent or guardian asks that their registration be invalidated. In order for the potential Member to use the Piccadilly.com interactive services, the parent or guardian must validate the account, as described in the e-mail. No information collected from Guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Piccadilly.com except as explicitly stated during registration for contests or promotions (and in that case, the information collected is used only for the specific contest or promotion).
Although Guests under 13 years of age may be allowed to participate in some contests and promotions, if such a Guest wins, notification and prizes are sent to the parent or guardian identified in the initial registration process. Publication of names, ages, or images for contest winners under 13 require parental or guardian consent.
We do not allow Guests under 13 years of age to receive direct marketing communications from Piccadilly.com or to be sent third party offers.
POLICIES FOR TEENS (INDIVIDUALS 13 TO 17 YEARS OF AGE)
Teens are required to provide the e-mail address of a parent or guardian and a notification message is sent to the parent or guardian of all Guests who are 13 to 17 years of age, which identifies the information supplied at Registration and allows the parent or guardian to be aware of and participate in the Guest's online experience.
USE OF IP ADDRESSES
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address.
Piccadilly.com collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When Guests request pages from Piccadilly.com, our servers log the Guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our terms of service or to protect our service, site, guests, or others. Some services within Piccadilly.com, such as certain message boards, may display IP addresses along with the message poster's name and message. Please review each service prior to use and only use those that disclose information you are comfortable with sharing.
USE OF COOKIES
What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites.
By showing how and when Guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs.
Piccadilly.com has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Piccadilly.com service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a cookie, visitors to Piccadilly.com always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. Information from cookies is sometimes attached to messages sent to our Guest Services department.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Piccadilly.com service will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering contests, or playing games.
You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Piccadilly.com does not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
Users should be aware that Piccadilly.com has no responsibility for, or control over, and therefore accepts no liability for the content or accuracy of sites linked from this page or sites that provide a link to this page. Therefore, be aware that when you are on Piccadilly.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from Piccadilly.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on an online map link, the "click" takes you off the Piccadilly.com web site. This includes links from advertisers and partners that may use Piccadilly.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.
Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via message boards or chat - that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Piccadilly.com strives to protect its users' personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.
Piccadilly.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond Piccadilly.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.
SECURITY
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our Guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Piccadilly.com can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
Remember to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using this site, you signify your assent to the Piccadilly.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Piccadilly.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
LAST UPDATED: 8/26/09
About Piccadilly
History
Corporate Information
News & Media
Careers
Quick Links
Online Ordering
Get all the updates on Piccadilly's current promotions and new menu items.
Sign Up
Text “PICCADILLY” or “MORRISONS” to 263333 for news & exclusive offers.
Message & Data rates apply. Click here for terms & conditions. Reply STOP to opt out.
Order Online!
Sorry! Online ordering is not available yet near you. Check back soon!
(change)
Your Location:
See Other Locations
Order Now!
